Another one bites the dust.
This is Libby from Channel 14 in Israel.
For all the Israeli fans, what message would you like to send for Israel?
And also, what do you think about Danny Avdea?
Well, I've been quoted on Danny already.
And they asked me what I thought about this season.
I said I believe he was an all-star.
I mean, he is an all-star.
He's playing exceptional basketball.
So that's that.
And then, I mean, if I have fans over there, I've never been there.
If I have fans over there, then, you know, I hope you have been following my career.
I hope I inspire people over there to not only want to be great in sports,
but I want to just be better in general in life.
So hopefully someday I can make it over there.
Like I said, I've never been over there, but I've heard nothing but great things.
And I appreciate the question.
Honestly, it's fuck LeBron and the rest of these clown coons.
Because at what point is there enough money for you to be like, nah, I'm good?